<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="txtHelp">
<![CDATA[
          <u><b>To Play</b></u>
          <p>Select New Game to start the quiz, then choose a level to play.
          Initially only the 1st level is unlocked. You unlock more levels by getting 7 or more questions right.
          For each question choose an answer from the options provided, if the answer is correct the
          game moves to the next question otherwise the selected option turns red.</p>
          <p>You can make another pick from the remaining options until you get the
          correct answer at which point the game proceeds to the next question.
          Once all questions have been answered a page will load displaying the results 
          and offering you a few options, such to sharing your scores with friends via 
          sms, facebook, whatsapp etc, uploading your scores to the Leadearboard, viewing the answers.</p>

          <u><b>Levels</b></u>
          <p>Each level there has a set of 10 questions. Only level one is unlocked, to unlock the
       	  other levels you have to get atleast 7 out of 10 questions right.
       	  More levels coming soon.</p>

          <u><b>Scores</b></u>
          <p>The scores submitted are ordered by level, result(Percentage of No of questions right) and
          the time taken to complete the game, the higher the level the higher the score.</p>

       	<b>Settings</b><br />
        	<u><b>Game Modes</b></u>
        	<p>Select the category you want to play.</p>
        	
        		<u><b>Simple</b></u>
        		<p>The game plays to the end until you have answered all the questions.</p>
        	
        		<u><b>Advanced Mode</b></u>
        		<p>If you get three questions wrong, the game ends - The number of lives is indicated by 3 mics at the top
        		<p>For every wrong answer provided the game vibrates,
        		 toggle the sounds/vibrate button to set you preference.</p>

        ]]>
    </string>

</resources>